He had been like this for a while.
He once said, Don't just let
any random object into the house.
And don't pick up any
strange things around the house.
Because the criminals that
he caught are plotting revenge.
He’s locked himself in the prayer room
and hasn't come down for a while now.
Just sitting there, chanting.
And lately.
There are strange noises upstairs.
Doesn't sound like him.
I called the Headman
and told him what's going on.
He's certain it's a curse.
He's taking me
to the shaman at the market.
I'll tell him what's going on.
Maybe he'll come do the ritual here.
Oh.
I have to hang up, Tuk.
The Headman's here to pick me up.
Okay, okay.
Singha.
I have to go out. I'll be right back.
If there's an emergency,
call Uncle Non at his house.
Run away.
Run away. Run away.
Auntie, glass noodle salad,
blue crabs, papaya salad, and two beers.
They want a discount on the chair fee.
Said there's a lot of them.
Complained that it's too expensive.
Ugh, hell no! No discount!
Don't like it?
Go sit somewhere else then.
Do they have any idea
how much I pay the mafia?
I can't say a damn thing.
Okay, I'm on it.
That guy is so annoying.
Hey, Foon.
Where are Singha and his guys?
Wow, holding her.
Zero respect for the husband.
Hmm.
you and your wife have a party.
Party at tonight.
Five o'clock.
I'll drive around and
pick you up at the hotel. Okay?
Ok. no problem.
- Where's the stuff?
- Oh.
Where's the stuff?
Damn. His Thai is better than mine.
No wonder he understood my gibberish.
Money, Money.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much. see you tonight.
Ok, Happy, happy.
- See you.
- Ok, See you.
Gonna go back and get some.
Hey, Singha.
This group is fucking easy.
The bastards aren't fussy at all.
- Easy, my ass.
- Hm!
Lately, these assholes are getting smart.
- Taking videos and shit.
- Ah!
Tonight, take all their fucking phones.
- Understood?
- Yeah, I get it. No need to teach me.
Ouch!
Just let me have a body like yours.
I'll get you back.
Anything else?
Joe.
- Why? Afraid you'll forget it?
- Yeah.
Here, Mom.
Oh, Thanks a lot.
Lock the door tonight, Mom.
I'm sleeping at Tun's shop
with Joe tonight.
- You should keep some for yourself.
- You keep it, Mom.
Don't worry about him.
He'll make some more tonight.
- Girls are all over him.
- Don't listen to her, Mom.
Big tips.
like they're taking Singha home
for the night.
Damn. How come nobody
ever wants to buy me out?
With a face like yours?
- Hey, you never know.
- Just go to sleep.
- Foreigners like exotic stuff.
- Go to sleep.
Enough, You guys stay and
help my mom with the beach chairs.
I'll deal with the Sergeant first.
So they won't be poking
around Tun's shop tonight.
Don't forget your medicine
tonight, Mom. Take it before bed.
Yeah, I won't forget.
Bye.
- You don't know anything.
- Go get...
Singha only made 1,500.
But I got mine yesterday.
- Hey!
- So how much did you get?
- Why are you guys even arguing?
- It's 1,900. Plus a free lunch box.
- Seriously, are you gonna keep arguing all day?
- You get fed, too.
He's just a big talker.
Hey, what the fuck are you guys doing?
Ganging up on a defenseless guy, huh?
What the fuck does this
have to do with you? Huh?
You piece of shit.
You.
Are you okay?
Umm.
You bastard!
Hey! You.
Hey.
Aren't you dead yet?
What's the hell?
Police!
- Here is your Blue Hawaii.
- Thank you.
Here I am. Oh.
Family favorite!
Here, take one each.
Thank you.
Hey.
I talked to Singha. We’re done dealing.
Damn.
What's gotten into you?
Suddenly want to be a saint?
Just thinking.
It's Singha.
He says the cops are starting
to sniff around.
Besides, there are a lot of
new drug dealers.
I'm not looking to sit behind bars
twiddling my thumbs.
I'm scared of prison, man.
So what are you guys going to do next?
There.
Ask Mr. Singha over there.
Isn't that right, Mr. Singha?
My friend Singha.
Little bro Singha!
Singha, you bastard!
- Huh? What?
- What the hell?
Tell her what we would do
if we weren't selling drugs.
Joe and I have been thinking
about it for a long time.
That once we save up enough money,
we'll open a bar
on the beach over there.
I already told Mr. Chatch
that I'm going to quit.
Is Mr. Chatch
gonna let you quit that easily?
He said it himself.
He’s letting another dealer
take care of it.
Seems like it’s those
new politicians who just stepped in.
They’re gonna deal it themselves.
Well, I hope it works out for you. Cheers!
One sip and you're already drunk?
I'm not buying this brand anymore.
Singha.
Are you okay?
Yes, I’m Okay.
- You’re okay?
- you okay.
Using a toast as a signal?
You’re a crafty one, tiger.
Setting the bait
for another deer again, I see.
And it’s not even a Thai deer.
It’s a reindeer straight-up imported.
Hey, is she a fortune teller?
- Watch my leg, man!
- That Sing guy or something?
You idiot! Hey, wait a minute!
You two know each other that well?
Cheers!
- Papi, I'm so cold.
- Alright, come here, baby.
- Cheers!
- Cheers! Cheers!
Boss, there's an MP candidate
asking to see you.
- Let him in.
- Yes, sir.
Come in.
Hello, Sir.
My name is Arnon Suphanpon.
Candidate number two.
If I make any mistakes.
Please let me know, P'Akkharaphon.
Drop the 'P'. I'm not your brother.
I'm older than your father.
What right do you have.
To compete with me?
You little punk!
You’re standing over me.
Get down here!
Get the hell down!
Yes, sir.
Don't you know a damn thing?
Who runs this place!
Do you have any idea.
What happened to the person
who applied before you?
He's pissing me off.
The next day,
I dumped his ass in the ocean.
Yes.
So, I intended to come
and pay my respects to you.
Stop talking. I'm not finished.
This town is mine.
Wait until I'm dead.
Then you can have your little thoughts.
I don't know what the hell
they're having an election for.
I'm winning anyway.
Who the hell do you work for?
I have no master.
I grew up all on my own, sir.
My father took his own life,
and my mother followed suit.
Spent two years
drifting in and out of psych wards.
Keep going until I tell you to stop.
Papi, Let me refill your glass.
It’s almost empty.
But I’m all better now, sir.
I have to make progress on my own, sir.
I work hard, I search,
and I do whatever it takes.
And if there's something I can't do,
I hire someone to get it done.
I just want to help
the people of this city, sir.
Whatever they can't do,
I want to do it for them.
All I'm asking for is a chance.
I have no intention
of stepping on your toes.
Tomorrow.
Pull your name out of this competition,
and mark my words!
Don't ever show your face here again.
Leave!
- What are you waiting for? Get out!
- Yes, sir. Thank you.
- Papi, don't be so stressed.
- Get going. Now!
- Yes.
- Let's have a drink.
Finish your glass.
Very good.
Hey, whose hair is this?
It feels like freaking broken glass! Huh!?
If I have to wait for you to die.
Then, I'm waiting.
It's coming!
Run away.
Hey.
- Yes.
- Hey, Serge.
According to eyewitnesses.
the Mayor’s close subordinate.
Said he looked like
he couldn't breathe before he passed away.
But noted there were two
or three hostesses present.
Who were constantly
pouring drinks for the Mayor.
And where are the hostesses now?
They’ve all run away, sir.
Oh, but before that.
The subordinates also mentioned that.
Mr. Arnon, candidate number two,
who’s running against the Mayor.
came to see him,
but left before the incident occurred.
Bring in all those girls for interrogation.
And get Arnon too.
Yes, sir.
Three female bodies were
found lying dead on the beach.
It looks like they’ve been dead
for a long time.
That's all for today.
Are you going to eat something first?
- No.
- Then hurry up.
- Mom...
- Hey.
- Oh.
- No need to call her, stay still.
Fuck.
The city page posted it this morning.
The mayor just checked in
with the Grim Reaper.
Holy crap, and they found
a woman's body in the sea too.
Holy shit!
It's a 'Death-Deaf' situation.
Holy shit, that’s so scary. Look at this!
Joe.
I think once we're done with
today's deliveries, we'd better to stop.
The vibe in town is fucking weird lately.
Cops are all over the place.
Yeah.
Alright, let me just finish
this batch first then.
Russia is fucking rushing me right now.
Tun is already waiting for me up there.
I’m gonna go with him.
Oh! Hey.
Can I bum a cigarette?
What happened between you
and those guys last night?
It's an old rival.
Haven't seen them in a long time.
Those guys you saw are just his subordinates.
Hey, about last night
when they shot at you.
So, you didn't get hit, right?
Nope, didn't get hit.
Is your father's name It?
Whoa, hey!
Out of nowhere,
you asked for my father's name.
- What the hell is this?
- Born on the ninth.
September.
Whoa, who are you?
Are you a scammer?
When did you see my card?
I think it’s time he came for you.
Watch yourself.
Stay away from the ones you love.
Run if you can.
Hide if you can.
This is the only warning I can give you.
What are you talking about?
Can I have a cigarette?
I'm not cooking today. I'm exhausted.
I’m not tired of the customers.
Moving canvas chairs
with Foon was tried.
It was just the two of us doing everything
I have no idea where Joe has disappeared to.
Mom.
Who is this guy?
Mom, do you know him?
His name. it's Dech.
He’s a former Sergeant.
He used to work under your dad.
He's a fellow disciple of Khao Ao,
and he was an informant for his father.
Later on, I heard he moved to work
around the Suphanburi area.
Your father sent him to
investigate a case in Dan Chang.
Wait, so why didn't he come back
to work for his father again?
Your father told me that when he returned,
Dech was rambling on about
being cursed with black magic.
It was those sorcerers
from the criminal's side.
He said he was going to kill everyone.
He told your father to watch his back.
Not long after that, he just vanished
maybe he didn't want to be
a burden to your father.
I only just ran into Dech
at the beginning of this year.
He talks sense.
I give him empty bottles all the time.
Mom, do you know what kind of case
he was investigating in Dan Chang?
And what exactly was the conflict about?
How should I know?
It's none of my business.
Hey, tomorrow I'm going to
have you take some fried squid.
To the temple as an offering for the monk.
They’re probably bored of eating
nothing but stir-fries and curries.
Sure, I'll take it there for you tomorrow.
Eat.
Blessings to you.
Hold the Phalo.
I need to watch my sugar right now.
Oh.
Please, brother.
Please, teacher.
Geez, Singha!
Just pick one. Is it Brother or teacher?
What brought you here today?
Long time no see!
Your house is practically next to the temple.
You even went to school here.
yet it never crosses your mind
to come by and make some merit.
Huh, seems like only
your mother ever shows up.
Well, here I am. My mother sent me
to offer this fried squid to you, Bhante.
Whoa!
Fried squid.
She was afraid you might be bored
of the usual dishes that the villagers offer.
Oh, yeah!
Always Phalo.
My diabetes can't take it anymore.
Oh, wow.
Your mother knows me best.
I can't tell anyone else.
You sure had a lot to say earlier!
There are so many people here today.
Is there some kind of event going on?
Oh, there’s no special event or anything.
But look over there.
I heard there are
some political candidates dropping by,
saying they're here to make merit,
pray, and donate money to the temple.
But if you ask me, their main goal.
Is more about campaigning for votes.
Donating money
and campaigning at the same time?
Who is that?
I heard his name is Arnon.
Luang Por, Today,
I would like to offer some funds to
support the temple and the religion.
But I might ask for your permission
to put up a sign in front of the temple.
What kind of sign is it?
It's a sign with my candidate number
it's not a big one.
I noticed the grass in front
of the temple is quite overgrown.
I'll have my workers
come to clean it up
and repaint the temple's main sign.
As long as it doesn't block
or obstruct anything.
And don't trouble the locals,
then go ahead.
Yes.
Thank you very much, Luang Por.
I’ll be taking my leave now.
Hey.
Oh.
Oh, aren't you going to sit?
It's bad karma
to stand over a monk like this.
Is that really okay?
Oh, come on!
You're already here, just sit down.
I have so many things to ask you.
Don’t you have anywhere else to be today?
Not at all. I'm free
and can chat for as long as you want.
Wow!
Teacher.
Are you thirsty?
Then, let me go get
some water for you first.
- So we can have a long chat.
- Hey, Singha.
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on.
Look,
If you keep me chatting
for just a little bit longer.
I’m going to miss my lunchtime.
And once that time passes.
I’ll be starving for the rest of the day.
Can you go ask someone else?
Because if you ask me today.
I won't eat again until tomorrow morning
I.
I'm not in a hurry at all,
and I still have so many things I want to ask you.
Oh, in a hurry.
And Joe is being so difficult.
he also wanted me to come and ask you.
It's bad enough with just you
asking now Joe has questions for me too?
- No errands either.
- No, I’m free all day.
Do you know Google?
Just type and ask whatever
you want to know. Tell Joe too.
It's almost time! I'm not gonna make it!
- You seem more rushed than I am.
- Yeah.
- Is it because of this fried squid?
Yep.
Okay, I get you now.
- I'm leaving now.
- Ah, okay.
I'll be back.
Come back early tomorrow morning.
Oh.
Is it past noon yet? Oh!
Hey Chan.
It’s exactly like you said, man.
It’s so freaking weird, holy shit!
Hello.
Sub-Lieutenant Wiriya Krajangwong,
reporting for duty.
Why didn't you go to the police station?
I went there, but the Inspector wasn't there.
They told me the Inspector
was working a case here, so I followed.
We'll talk about that later.
The reason I called you all here today.
Is because I want to show you something.
You're not gonna believe this.
The mayor's stomach.
It was full of nothing but alcohol
and a whole pile of hair!
This is so freaking weird.
How the hell did he even eat that?
Inspector,
Excuse me, sir.
Are you saying he was killed by black magic?
But I didn't want to believe it either.
If I hadn't seen it with my own eyes.
And performed the autopsy myself.
I wouldn't believe this shit at all.
I've only ever seen this
in movies or videos.
Then don't believe it just yet!
Find whoever did this.
So we can find out who's behind all this.
I don't even know how to write this report.
Inspector, there’s someone
waiting to see you on the second floor.
Sergeant.
Show the Lieutenant to her desk.
Yes, sir.
Lieutenant,
we'll talk later.
Yes.
- This way, Lieutenant.
- Yes.
Greetings, Inspector.
I'm Arnon Suphanphon.
Mayoral Candidate Number two.
Running as an independent candidate.
I heard that you wanted
to question me further, Inspector.
Yes.
I appreciate your help with this.
On the night of the incident
- Did Mr. Arnon...
- Excuse me!
Before I forget.
I have some bulletproof vests. And...
tasers that I'd like to
donate to the station.
And if you're short on anything else,
I can donate directly to the station.
I am more than happy to be of service.
Let's continue.
On the night of the incident.
before Mayor Akkarapol passed away.
what did you talk to him about, Mr. Arnon?
And before that.
Did you know him personally, Mr. Arnon?
No, I didn't.
I just happened to be having dinner at that hotel.
I saw that he was there.
the number one candidate.
So, I just wanted to go over
and pay my respects.
I introduced myself and then left.
That’s all. It was nothing.
He was a very generous man.
Very commanding presence.
It's a shame his life was cut a bit short.
But then again, not that short.
He was old.
He's finally at rest now. At rest.
And after that?
Where did you go next, Mr. Arnon?
I went home to feed my insects.
I keep quite a lot of them.
I love watching them devour their prey.
It makes me happy.
Lieutenant, are you ready to get to work?
Then, I need you to dig up
everything you can find on this Mr. Arnon.
I want it in full detail.
Everything else can wait.
Yes, sir.
- Arnon.
- Yes.
How’s the election going?
Yes, sir.
In the next election,
whoever your party runs is bound to win anyway.
And what about the mafia guys?
It’s all been taken care of.
No problems. But if any come up,
just let me know.
As long as those Russians and
Chinese stay out of it, we’re good.
I’ll deal with them all
at once after the job is done.
Keep my name out of this, you hear me?
Yes.
I understand.
Okay, park here.
It was a bumpy ride,
but we're finally here.
Thank you.
Hey, Singha.
I think you should go and
pay your respects to the Buddha."
Your birthday is coming up soon.
they say this year’s
energy is particularly strong.
It’s believed that your 'karmic debtors'
will have full power
to claim what’s owed.
Go on, go offer some prayers.
And have the Abbot perform
a water blessing for you.
Good luck will stay,
and bad luck will turn into a blessing.
I've been through
a lot of bad times already.
I'd better get back to the shop now.
It doesn't hurt to believe in this stuff,
you know.
Like they say if you don't believe it,
at least don't disrespect it.
You still don't believe me.
Fine.
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
Drive safely.
Holy shit!
That person the one
we performed the ritual for.
I didn't realize
he held such a powerful position.
It’s both risky and difficult.
You need to pay us more.
See? It was worth it.
- Nothing will stand in your way anymore.
- Fine, fine.
How much do you want?
I'll transfer it to you now.
Double the amount.
We'll split it among ourselves.
There’s one more thing.
The water ghost I keep it came
and whispered to me.
That someone is keeping a 'Phi Ha'
and it's lurking around this town.
Should I take care of it now?
It’s actually quite powerful.
Well, if it gets in our way, deal with it.
But it won't be cheap.
Just get lost already.
And don't show your face
around here too often.
Can't all be damn businessmen!
Property in Bang Lamung.
The beachfront plot.
Across from the Laemchabang Hotel.
Sold by owner.
It’s all been cleared up, sir.
We had a proxy do the talking.
We closed the deal at 250 million.
No problems at all.
If anything comes up, just let me know.
MP Banjong.
Keep me out of this.
Destroy all the evidence.
Yes, sir.
Hey!
Did you kill my boss?
Who's your boss?
You’ve got the wrong guy.
Don't say a word.
Go to hell!
- Hey!
- Hey, hurry up!
Where to?
Damn it!
Who are you?
We'll talk about it later.
Shit! Where the fuck is he?
There are two groups of suspects.
One group assassinated Mr. Arnon.
A stranger appeared,
helped Arnon wipe them all out,
then vanished.
Wait, Sarge.
Rewind the footage.
Yes, sir.
Wow, that was a direct hit!
He's tough as nails, isn't he?
Is he using black magic or something?
Zoom in more, Sarge.
Zoom in again.
More.
Not a single scratch?
What kind of body armor is that?
It’s so thin!
Getting hit by an M4 like that
he should’ve at least been knocked down.
That's the limit, sir.
The image is pixelated now.
Can you make it any clearer?
I can't, sir.
This machine has reached its limit.
Let me try running it
through the editing rig
and some apps to see what I can do.
It should help a bit.
Hey, Kris!
Do you remember that
rubber plantation case in the South?
The one we were assigned to.
"Of course I remember.
How could I forget?
How did it go again?
I didn't go in with you
when you raided the place.
Well, at first, we split up
and went in separately.
I got to that bastard Chat first.
The bastard actually fought back.
So I emptied the whole clip into him.
By the time I got to him,
the bastard had vanished without a trace.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I shot him right in the chest.
In the end, I just had to
come back and write the report.
No one believed a damn word I said.
In the end, we never caught the bastard.
I've been stuck ever since.
I haven't really followed up
on that case since
So, he just vanished?
No. Someone spotted him
all the way down in Nakhon.
He was killed by another sorcerer.
They shot him right in the mouth
so he finally died.
But hey, why are you asking?
I’m working on a case right now.
And there are some
strange similarities to that one.
That’s all I wanted to ask.
Sorry to bug you.
I'll give you a call if anything else comes up.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thank god the 'hero' was here to save me.
A villain like you was absolutely useless.
Hey, Ms. Foon! Open your damn eyes
and look at what this villain is carrying!
This shit is heavy as hell.
You wanna come and carry it for me?
Hey Foon, don't forget.
My mom is going to the temple
to make merit tomorrow morning.
Mom asked you to help set up the shop.
Got it.
Sure thing. I might as well
be your wife at this point.
Oh, dear Singha, my beloved husband.
Sure, make me do all the work,
'dear husband'.
Trust me,
Singha doesn't want you as a wife.
Trust me, fucking a sea urchin
or some mud
would be way more fun for him
than being with you.
Wow, look at Mr. Handsome.
Such a hero!
- Thank you.
- Gong Yoo.
Marijoe? Oh, look at you!
So handsome, you dog tick!
You dog tick!
Let's take a photo.
It's been a while, come on!
- Let's put this on socials.
- Sure!
- Socials.
Come on. One, two.
Great.
My hair looks like a rooster.
What the hell is this haircut?
That's just how the sea breeze is.
- Huh.
- Hey.
- What?
- Joe, look at this.
Where?
Here.
Whoa, who's this 'handsome guy' in the glasses?
Here!
Behind Singha.
Shit!
Hey, what are you guys
gossiping about me?
What are you guys watching?
- You tell him. You tell Singha yourself!
- Give me that! Let me see.
- Just tell him already!
- Look, it's scary as hell.
You slapped me.
Damn, it's nothing.
The light just hit
your lens. It’s just a reflection.
Are you guys just imagining things?
What kind of fucking ghost
comes out during the day?
There’s something wrong
with your camera.
But I just bought it!
Even ghosts doing overtime
can come out during the day.
Night.
That shit can show up whenever it wants!
- Hey Foon, get over here.
- What? What?
- Send me that photo.
- Why?
- I'm calling P'Jack
- Jack who?
Jack from The Ghost Radio.
Pong?
Are they friends?
- Or do they hate each other?
- They’re having a fight right now.
They’re having a fight now?
Uncle.
This is a Bia Gae.
Keep it on you at all times.
The mercury inside will protect you.
Hurry up and go straight home.
Don't come out if you don't have to.
Uncle.
Is my father still alive?
That's just the karma he has to face.
For people like us,
once we dive into the occult.
the dark arts. black magic.
Once you step into the dark side.
There's no easy way out.
Pull yourself together!
It's getting seriously dangerous lately.
Run away.
Father.
Let the Buddha's teachings be your guide.
Do only good deeds.
You need to get as far away as possible.
And don't come back.
Someone you love is going to die.
Run away.
Why must I run away? Father?
Why? Why should I be afraid?
Its power is overwhelming.
You can't win against it.
It will find you.
It's coming.
Who, Father?
Who’s coming? Tell me who!